<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Zelaf's Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[I write about projects, problems and my life.]]></description><link>http://blog.zelaf.eu</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 21:38:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://blog.zelaf.eu/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Now migrated!]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Finally I got propper blog hosting! Now I use HubPress (<a href="https://github.com/HubPress/hubpress.io" class="bare">https://github.com/HubPress/hubpress.io</a>)</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It feels limited in what it can do. Especially in the writing. BUT unlike other GitHub Pages hostable, it has web based writing&#8230;&#8203; You can write the text in your browser. I think it&#8217;s a wrapper to ghost which is really nice actually! I can&#8217;t turn text into links but I have to post them seperatly which kinda sucks.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_titles">Titles</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_great">Great</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Instead of using headers like in HTML you use '='.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I can also insert code snipets</p>
</div>
<div class="listingblock">
<div class="content">
<pre>== Titles

=== Great</pre>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I quite like this.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Hopefully writing will be easier in the future and maybe even more entries to come!</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://blog.zelaf.eu/2016/09/16/Now-migrated.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.zelaf.eu/2016/09/16/Now-migrated.html</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[School related problems]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>Problems can cause alot of extra work and make you really tired. So when the town denies your request to pay for residential at a school&#8230;&#8203; You don&#8217;t get much to do. Go up play games or watch a movie, eat and then do that throughout the day and then go to bed&#8230;&#8203; Repeat&#8230;&#8203;. This gets boring after a few days&#8230;&#8203; But after a few weeks it gets repetative and it&#8217;s driving me nuts.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I&#8217;m starting to have nightmares at nights&#8230;&#8203; Might not be connected to me not able to go to school, but I&#8217;m sitting at home all day long doing practicly nothing&#8230;&#8203; I watched 3 harry potter movies in 1 sitting <strong>in order</strong>. Life is getting boring and I don&#8217;t have much to do. I feel like I should go do something but what is there to do? I&#8217;m soon 16 and I "go" to "gymnasiet", think of it as high school or college if you wish. It&#8217;s a town away and I had problems taking the bus to a school inside my town already so I&#8217;m gonna have even more problems going to there. It&#8217;s a 10 minute bus ride, 30 minute train ride and a 30 minute walk. It&#8217;s alot and I just can&#8217;t handle that. The fear of being lost or taking the wrong train is just killing me. Either way, we decided to do an appeal against the decition to not pay it and now that&#8217;s in the work.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In the mean time I just got to pull through. I should start doing walks again&#8230;&#8203; Maybe around 11:00 AM and then another one at 3:00 PM that should keep me energized and maybe even happier. I&#8217;m writing this at 8:30 roughly so I guess I&#8217;ll go have some breakfast and then I&#8217;ll prepare for a walk.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Thanks for reading I hope I&#8217;ll get to migrate the blog to a propper website soon.</p>
</div>]]></description><link>http://blog.zelaf.eu/2016/09/14/School-related-problems.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.zelaf.eu/2016/09/14/School-related-problems.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[When your stomach hurts]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>I&#8217;ve had some small problems with my stomach before. Probably due to stress but when you don&#8217;t eat much for a long while your stomach gets a bit more empty then usual. When you then eat something really bad and you vomit you practicly make it completely empty&#8230;&#8203; I think this is what happened to me, after I vomited I were scared to eat because of the fear of it happening again. So I believe my acid levels got higher and higher and now I&#8217;ve had abdominal pains for almost 4 weeks. I feel a piercing constant hurting feeling as well as nausea on the mornings and then before I go to bed I feel a strong nasuea feeling. It&#8217;s horrible to say the least&#8230;&#8203; How do I solve this?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I went to the doctor a few days ago and I told her about my problem. She then told me to try to get some medication that reduces the acid levels in my stomach. So I did that and now I take those when I wake up and around dinner time. I also force myself to eat, at first I only ate yogurt and ["Filmjölk"](<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Filmj%C3%B6lk"" class="bare">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Filmj%C3%B6lk"</a> target="_blank). It started out okay then my stomach got kinda "loose" but I only ate that for about 2 days, small portions every now and then when I started to feel nauseated.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It has gotten better and I do feel better when I eat, so the reason explained above is probably the cause of why I&#8217;ve been feeling like this for such a long time&#8230;&#8203; It was just stupid of me that I didn&#8217;t eat anything propperly for around 3 weeks and didn&#8217;t do anything about it straight away.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I hope that I will feel better soon and that I can do continue to work on my project because now, my stomach hurts to the point that I&#8217;m scared of going out because I constantly think "What if I vomit?" so I&#8217;ve been staying inside eating small portions of food for a few days now and hopefully it will be better soon.</p>
</div>]]></description><link>http://blog.zelaf.eu/2016/07/06/When-your-stomach-hurts.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.zelaf.eu/2016/07/06/When-your-stomach-hurts.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>I got a new blog up and running now&#8230;&#8203; I wont update it too much&#8230;&#8203; Maybe a few times a week to say where I&#8217;ve been and such. I could integrate it into my Adobe Portfolio website so maybe I&#8217;ll do that!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>For the time being I hope my problems with the domain and HSTS will get solved and that I get a better future&#8230;&#8203; In the mean time I hope you&#8217;re gonna have a great day too!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Edit: Fixed the error by clearing ALL my browser data&#8230;&#8203; Luckily I could save my passwords&#8230;&#8203; x3
Edit2: Maybe not all :(</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>If you&#8217;re wondering about the URL it&#8217;s because I&#8217;m hosting it on my Cozy Cloud provided by <a href="http://cozy.io" class="bare">http://cozy.io</a> you should check them out yourselves if you&#8217;re interested in getting a personal cloud filled with features that other users have created!</p>
</div>]]></description><link>http://blog.zelaf.eu/2016/07/05/New-blog.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.zelaf.eu/2016/07/05/New-blog.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>